http://www.fumcsalisbury.org/privacy.html

Visit
New Here?
Calendar
Ecclesia (monthly newsletter)
Legacy Giving
Where Does it Go?
Scholarships
Privacy
Media
Privacy
At First United Methodist Church of Salisbury, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Any information that we collect is used to provide the best possible experience for users. By using this web site maintained by First United Methodist Church, you agree to the terms set forth below. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this website.A. Collection & UseFirst United Methodist Church of Salisbury recognizes the privacy concerns of users of our website on the Internet and the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected from them. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as a visitor’s name, address, email address, telephone number, or credit card information is automatically collected on our websites. Such information is collected only when it is knowingly and voluntarily submitted, and First United Methodist Church uses such information only for the purpose for which it was submitted, unless we disclose other uses in this policy or at the time of collection.We maintain reasonable and appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of such information in our possession. First United Methodist Church does not sell personally identifiable information to third parties. First United Methodist Church will not disclose, sell, trade, or rent personal information it collects to outside parties. We reserve the right to monitor visitor traffic patterns and website usage to help us develop the design and layout of our website to enhance your online experience.B. Privacy PolicyFirst United Methodist Church of Salisbury reviews our Privacy Policy periodically, and we reserve the right, at our discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. This page should be reviewed from time to time, so that you can be aware of any changes. If you want to communicate with us about our Privacy Policy, email us at webmaster@fumcsalisbury.org, or write us at: First United Methodist Church, 217 S. Church St., Salisbury, NC 28144.
Visit
217 S. Church St.Salisbury, NC 28144
worship
Sundays 8:30 and 11am
Contact us
(704) 636-3121webmaster@fumcsalisbury.orgFax: (704) 637-2933
Our mission is to make and nurture Christian Disciples through the presence and power of God.
New Here?
Ecclesia (monthly newsletter)
Where Does it Go?
Scholarships
Privacy
Media
